

# Ivan Zabrodin

E-mail: xvanx84@gmail.com Website: <a href="http://ivanzabrodin.com/">http://ivanzabrodin.com/</a>
Phone: +79119423159 Address: Saint-Petersburg, Russia

# Work experience

Molinos 20.09.2017 — Present

Ruby on Rails Developer

- Creating web applications with RubyOnRails
- Working with API (own, with full documentation, and using someone else's as usual)
- Building a project architecture
- · Assessing the amount and timing of tasks for the backend
- Querying the database (PostgreSQL)
- Implementation of VK and Telegram bots

CashCowPro 25.02.2017 — 31.05.2018

Ruby on Rails Developer

**Description:** responsible for a part of developing highly distributed Ruby on Rails web application for a high performance, high traffic, advanced interactive site that attracts a lot of visitors per day, by providing technical documentation for various products online.

**Overall Team Size: 4** 

#### Project:

- Analytics platform and software tool for online sellers
- Back-end
- -- Ruby 2.2.3
- -- Ruby on Rails 4.2
- Environment:
- -- MySQL
- -- ORM: ActiveRecord
- -- Authentication: Devise
- -- Capistrano
- -- Sidekiq, Redis, Git, Haml

### **Brabens Development**

04.05.2016 - 15.02.2017

Junior Ruby on Rails Developer

Description: back-end developing using Ruby on Rails, implementing parsers and crawlers for projects.

**Overall Team Size:** 3

#### **Projects:**

- Search For Manuals Online
- Search For Alternative apps Online.

Ivan Zahrodin

- Back-end
- -- Ruby 2.3
- -- Ruby on Rails 4.2
- Environment:
- -- PostgreSQL
- -- ORM: ActiveRecord
- -- Testing Framework: Rspec (with FactoryGirl)
- -- Authentication: Devise-- App server: Puma
- -- Sideqik

### Qualifications

#### **SUMMARY:**

Middle software development engineer featuring expertise in Ruby on Rails, web frameworks and other programming languages, a passion for Web 2.0 trends, APIs, mashups and other disruptive technologies.

- Strong knowledge of Web standards and protocols
- Understanding of relation model and its implementations
- Knowledges in RESTful API
- Writing technical documentations

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS:**

Front-end:HTML5/CSS3, Sass, Haml, JQuery, Twitter Bootstrap

Back-end:Ruby(Ruby on Rails, Sinatra), RDBMS (MySQL, PostgreSQL), RSpec, Nginx, Puma, Redis, Sidekiq, Docker

Cloud infrastructure systems: Heroku, AWS

Tools: Vim, Jira, Trello, Slack

Version control: Git

Automating software building: Bundler, Capistrano, Mina, Rake

#### **CORE PRINCIPLES:**

- Follow cs/software design principles
- Design before implementation
- The team is greater than any single person
- Testing leads to stable maintainable code

#### Language Skills:

- Russian Native
- English Intermediate

## Education

Ruby / Rails Developer

Geekbrains.ru

### Ruby / Rails Developer

Ivan Zabrodin 2

# Interests

- Sport, workouts
- Foreign languages learning

van Zabrodin 3